One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I don't believe it!
Olacak iş değil!
Leader of the Mt. Atama Thieves, Ashura Doji
Atama Dağı Haydutları'nın Lideri Ashura Doji
The Oniwabanshu captains...
Oniwabanshu...
and the Mimawari-gumi's, too...
ve Mimawari-gumi komutanlarının çoğu...
Most of them are down!
yerde yatıyor!
Daikoku!
Daikoku-san!
Lord Kazekage!
Kazekage-sama!
Captain Hotei!
Komutan Hotei!
So that's what the legendary yakuza is capable of, huh?!
Efsanevi yakuza liderinin gücü mü bu?
He resisted the effects of the ice ogre, but still took advantage of its power!
Buz şeytanına dönüşmeye karşı koyup bunu lehine kullandı!
I think I'm beginning to understand...
Neden dünyanın Wano'dan bu kadar korktuğunu...
why Wano has been so feared...
şimdi daha iyi anladım.
Boss!
Patron!
Boss Hyogoro!
Patron Hyogoro!
What are you waiting for, Yatappe?!
Neyi bekliyorsun, Yatappe?
Empty your mind!
Zihnini boşalt!
If I turn into an ice ogre...
Buz şeytanına dönüşürsem...
I know!
Biliyorum!
Just give me a second!
Bana az süre tanıyın!
I'm gonna do it!
Yapacağım,
I'll do it right now!
birazdan yapacağım!
Of course it's difficult...
Zorlanmakta haklı.
After all, that man...
Siz bizim...
is like a father to us!
babamız sayılırsınız.
Tsunagoro, cut me down right now!
Tsunagoro, tereddüte düşmeden kes beni!
Boss Hyogoro...
Patron Hyogoro...
I'll join you soon!
ben de peşinizden geliyorum!
Omasa!
Omasa!
Dammit!
Kahretsin!
Isn't there any way you can finish in time, Mr. Tanuki?!
Nerede kaldınız, Tanuki-san?!
I can't fight it anymore, either!
Benim de artık takatım kalmadı!
There's no saving me now!
Yolun sonuna geldim.
Just do it!
Çabuk yap!
Don't let me...
Sizi...
Boss Omasa!
Sefir Omasa!
Don't let me hurt you all!
Sizi incitmek istemiyorum!
Mr. Tanuki!
Tanuki-san!
Surely the cure is ready by now?!
Daha ilacı bitiremediniz mi?
The entire floor...
Yine bu kat...
all of our companions...
ve dostlarımız...
will succumb to the ice ogre once more!
buz şeytanının esiri olacak!
Your Awesomeness!
Queen-sama!
We work for you, man... Why do we have to die from your virus, too?!
Sizin için çalışıyoruz be... Niye biz de virüsünüzden ölmek zorundayız?
Shut your mouths, you lowlifes!
Kesin sesinizi ezikler!
You punks have outlived your usefulness!
Artık sizden bir cacık olmaz.
Listen up!
Dinleyin!
If I can't use you, you're as good as trash!
Hiçbir işe yaramazsanız çöpsünüz demektir.
The ice ogre virus is my crowning achievement!
Buz şeytanı virüsü benim şaheserim!
If anything, it was made especially for you!
Bir nevi sizin için yapıldı.
Hey, Pleasures!
Hey, Hazcılar!
You guys already lost the ability lottery!
Siz çoktan yetenek bahsini kaybettiniz.
Now you're nothing but cackling cannon fodder!
Gülmekten başka bir şey yapmayan oksijen israflarısınız.
Th-That's awful!
A-Ağır oluyor!
Hey, Waiters!
Hey, Fırsatçılar!
You can wait all you like, but there're no more smile fruits coming!
Sonsuza dek bekleseniz de yeni Gülücükler gelmeyecek!
You guys lost your chance to be somebody!
Yani, yetenek kazanma şansınızı kaybettiniz!
The Eternal Waiters.
Ebediyen Fırsatçılar.
It's a fitting name, since all you can do is wait!
Adı üstünde tek işiniz beklemek.
The only way you layabouts can be of use to the mighty Beast Pirates...
Siz avellerin Canavar Korsanları'na katkı sağlayabilmesinin tek yolu...
is by at least becoming an ogre before you die.
buz şeytanına dönüşerek...
That way you can do something worth a damn with your final moments!
giderayak bir işe yaraması!
So are you saying... we should just die?!
Sanki bize öl diyorsunuz.
Oh! Now you get it!
Evet, diyorum.
We already have plenty of troops.
Denizde kum, bizde adam.
What an awful thing to say!
Ayıp ama, böyle söylenir mi?
No way...
Olamaz...
You had your chance!
Size bir şans verdim!
Those antibodies could still save some of you!
Antikor birkaçınız kurtarabilir!
Dammit! I'm not gonna die without a fight!
Sikeyim! Ölecek değilim!
Cut down every ice ogre, samurai and allies alike!
Dönüşen siper arkadaşlarınız olsun, samuraylar olsun, alayını kesin!
Now that's what I'm talkin' about!
Kim tutar sizi?
Fight your asses off to survive!
Hayatta kalmak için götünüzü yırtın!
His treatment of his men is sickening!
Karşı tarafın ast üst ilişkisi şahane.
Indeed it is.
Evet, hem de nasıl.
Hey, you damn samurai!
Siz oradaki samuraylar,
Maybe you don't realize who you're protecting over there,
korumalık yapmak iyi hoş da...
but in case you forgot, that tanuki...
o tanuki...
is a pirate, just like us!
bir korsan.
Queen...
Queen...
Synthesizing that many antibodies in such a short amount of time?!
Kısacık sürede tonla antikor mu üretecek?
Don't make me laugh!
İmkânı yok!
He probably just gave himself the cure and bailed!
Antikoru kendine enjekte edip tüymemişse bir şey bilmiyorum!
He's nothing like you villains!
Size benzemez o!
Are you sure about that?
Öyle mi?
Pirates aren't known for being loyal!
Korsanların işi arkadan vurmaktır.
Boss Hyogoro!
Patron Hyogoro!
I'll be right behind you!
Ben de yakında size katılacağım!
Don't be so hasty to follow me...
Vaden dolunca katılırsın.
– Big Boss!
– Patron!
Farewell...
Elveda...
Wait!
Bekle!
Don't try and stop me, Mr. Tanuki!
Durdurmayın beni, Tanuki-san!
We have no other choice!
Bunu yapmak lazım.
Just wait!
Bekle biraz,
I'll save him right now!
şimdi onu kurtaracağım.
Boss! Swallow it!
Patron, yut onu.
Thank goodness! We made it just in time!
Şükür yetiştim.
B-Boss...
P-Patron...
Alright! It's working!
Harika, işe yaradı!
Your body is warming up!
Vücudun yanması normal.
Boss Hyogoro!
Patron Hyogoro!
Are you all right?!
İyi misiniz?!
Yeah...
Evet...
It worked!
İşe yaradı!
I knew you could do it, Mr. Tanuki!
Tanuki-san, size güvenim tamdı!
Miyagi! Tristan! On the double!
Miyagi, Tristan, acele edin!
Right away, Dr. Chopper!
Peki, Dr. Chopper!
What's that?
Bu...
It's all set, Dr. Chopper!
Her şey hazır, Dr. Chopper!
Alright! Let's do it!
Pekâlâ, hadi yapalım!
Dr. Chopper! Just give the order!
Dr. Chopper, emrinizi bekliyoruz!
– A cannon?!
– Top mu?!
Chopperphage...
Chopper'ın Faj...
Nebulizer!
Nebulizatörü!
N E B U L I Z E R C H O P E R P H A G E
N E B U L İ Z A T Ö R Ü C H O P E R I N F A J
Fire!
Ateş!
Everyone! Inhale the mist!
Herkes sisi içine çeksin!
What do you think you're doing, you damn tanuki?!
Ne yaptığını sanıyorsun, tanuki?!
The pinnacle of my work... What have you done!?
Şaheserime ne yaptın öyle?
Individually handing out medicine to thousands of soldiers would be impossible!
Kattaki sürüyle savaşçıya ilacı teker teker vermenin olanağı yok!
So I created my own virus using the antibodies!
Ben de antikordan kendi virüsümü yarattım!
You what?!
Ne dedin?
A good virus can counteract a bad virus!
İyi bir virüs, kötü bir virüsü yenebilir!
This way, everyone just needs to breathe in the mist to be cured!
Bu yolla herkes sisi soluyarak ilacı alabilir!
You're just some ship doctor from a backwater pirate crew...
Senin gibi ufacık bir korsan tayfasının doktoru...
Where did you learn something like this?!
böyle becerileri nereden edindi?
We scattered all over the world to train for moments like this!
Biz dünyanın dört bir yanına dağılıp kendimizi eğittik!
You even cured my own guys of ice ogre!
Benim adamlarımı bile virüsten kurtardın!
What gives you the right?!
Üstüne vazife mi?
Who in their right mind would use a virus as a weapon?!
Virüsler savaşta kullanılmaz!
There's no way to control it!
İşler kontrolden çıkar!
I am not gonna be lectured on ethics by a damn tanuki!
Bir tanukiden etik dersi alacak değilim!
Who the hell do you take me for?!
Karşında kim var sanıyorsun?
Pleasures?!
Hazcılar?!
Why?!
Neden?
What the hell are you doing?!
N'apıyorsunuz lan siz?
Stay out of this, you rats!
Çekilin önümden ezik sürüsü!
Up yours, Queen!
Kapa çeneni, Queen!
You nearly killed our brothers...
Tanuki-san kurtarmasaydı...
but Mr. Tanuki here saved our asses!
kardeşlerimiz ölüyordu!
We'd rather die side-by-side with the guy who saved us...
Bir manyağın emrinde ölmektense...
instead of being killed by our crazy-ass boss!
bizi kurtaranın yanında ölürüz!
Ain't that right, boys?!
Değil mi, beyler?
Thank you, tanuki!
Sağ ol, tanuki!
Tanuki!
Tanuki!
We are in your debt, Mr. Tanuki!
Size bir can borcumuz var, Tanuki-san!
Mr. Tanuki... Thank you!
Tanuki-san, teşekkür ederim!
You're really somethin' else, little tanuki.
Etkileyici birisin, tanuki.
– Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki!
– Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki! Tanuki!
Go to hell, Queen!
Geber, Queen!
You little shits!
Mallar!
What the hell is this?!
Bu ne ulan?
Not bad at all, tanuki!
Aferin sana, tanuki.
Now let him have it.
Sana saldım.
Thanks, Marco!
Sağ ol, Marco.
There's just one more thing that I wanna say!
Demek istediğim bir şey daha var.
Tanuki!
Tanuki!
Rumble!
Gümbürtü!
Monster Point!
Canavar Noktası!
– Get him!
– Hakla onu!
You got this!
Yaparsın!
What?!
Ne?!
I'm not a tanuki!
Ben tanuki değilim!
We're so sorry!
Özür dileriz!
Right-Brain Tower Inside the Dome
Kubbenin İçi Sağ Beyin Kulesi
There's a bunch of space between each floor of the castle!
Kalenin her katında geniş bir tavan arası var.
No one'll see us there!
Kimse bizi orada göremez!
Okay!
Tamam!
Lord Momonosuke! Please hold on just a little longer!
Momonosuke-sama, biraz daha sabredin!
Momonosuke, are you okay?
Momonosuke-kun, rahat mısın orada?
I am not okay...
Hiç değilim...
What do you mean?!
Neden öyle dediniz?!
I am not okay. I feel awful.
Hiç rahat hissetmiyorum.
I hate myself.
Kendimden nefret ediyorum.
Everyone gives me too much credit!
Beni gözünüzde büyütüyorsunuz!
I... I...
Ben... Ben...
I am frivolous, stupid...
Ben değersiz, aptal...
weak, foolish, and I make myself sick...
çelimsiz ve ahmağım. Kendimi hiç sevmiyorum.
Lord Momonosuke, I think you're amazing!
Siz müthişsiniz efendim!
I am not amazing at all!
Müthiş falan değilim.
Even if you're small now,
Şu an minik olsanız da...
I know that you'll grow up to be a proper shogun one day!
bir gün büyük bir şogun olacaksınız!
You'll be an even greater man than Kozuki Oden ever was!
Kozuki Oden'i bile gölgede bırakacak muhteşem biri olacaksın sen!
I am not... I am not...
Ben öyle... Ben öyle...
I am not amazing at all!
Öyle müthiş biri olamam!
What?!
Ne?!
An eel?!
Yılan balığı mı?
Lord Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-sama!
Why do you look like that?
Bu görünüş...
This is what happens to Lord Momonosuke when his emotions run high.
Heyecanlandığı zaman buna dönüşüyor.
Huh?
Heh?
Did you eat a devil fruit or something?
Şeytan meyvesi mi yedin acaba?
Indeed, I did...
Evet, yedim...
Guest Parlor Inside the Castle
Kalenin İçi Misafir Odası
Speaking of Kaido...
Kaido demişken...
Back when the Marines had him held captive...
bir ara Denizciler'in eline düşmüştü.
Vegapunk extracted Kaido's hereditary elements...
Vegapunk da bu fırsatı kullanarak Kaido'nun soy faktörlerini çıkarıp...
and used them to create an artificial devil fruit.
insan yapımı bir şeytan meyvesi üretmişti.
The government requested that he hand over the fruit,
Hükûmet onu teslim etmesini istemişti.
but since Vegapunk considered it a disappointing failure,
Ama sonuçları beğenmediğinden başarısızlık olarak görüp...
it was stored at Punk Hazard long term.
meyveyi uzun zaman Punk Hazard'da saklı tutmuştu.
Why bring that up now?
Ne diye şimdi bunu dile getiriyorsun?
Punk Hazard was blown up.
Punk Hazard havaya uçtu.
The fruit should be gone now.
Geriye bir şey kalmamıştır.
I can only hope it was destroyed in that explosion,
Patlamada yok olduysa sorun yok...
but Marine Branch G-5 reported that one facility was still in operation...
ama G-5'in bildirdiğine göre bir tesis hâlâ faaliyetteymiş.
I'm just grateful... that it was a failure.
Başarısızlıkla sonuçlanmasına sevindim sadece.
"Treasury"
"Hazine Odası"
Who treated our wounds?
Kim bizi tedavi etti?
I do not know...
Bilmiyorum.
But I believe I may have seen someone...
Kimdi gördüm galiba.
No, it must have been a dream...
Yok, hayal görmüşümdür.
After all, it could not have been...
Öyle bir şey olamaz.
Sir Luffy and his allies are engaging Kaido in our stead.
Luffy-dono ve dostları Kaido'yla savaşıyor.
We should not stay here and sit idly by!
Burada oturup duramayız.
The battle for this island rages on!
Adadaki savaş daha bitmedi!
Let us move!
Gidiyoruz!
We still have life left to give!
Hâlâ ruhumuzu teslim etmedik!
You guys!
Görünüşe göre...
You look like hell!
çok pis dayak yemişsiniz.
How I've missed you all!
Sizi çok özledim.
You're so much older now!
Ne kadar yaşlanmışsınız.
L-Lord Oden!
Oden-sama!
Lord Oden?
Oden-sama?
It's no wonder you're surprised!
Şaşırmanız gayet doğal.
Toki sent me here to the future with the help of her ability!
Toki beni gücüyle geleceğe yolladı.
I'll explain everything later.
Sonra açıklarım.
It's a long story!
Uzun hikâye.
Lord Oden!
Oden-sama!
So that is why you are here!
Sizsiniz demek!
Sorry for being late!
Geç kaldığım için kusura bakmayın.
But we don't have time to catch up right now!
Tekrar buluşmamızın sevincini sonra yaşarız.
Now come!
O gün...
We go to Kaido, the man we failed to kill on that fateful day!
deviremediğimiz Kaido'yla yüzleşmeye gidelim!
Of course!
Elbette!
We are with you!
Sizinle geleceğiz.
That has been our wish from the beginning!
Daima tek arzumuz buydu!
Let us depart!
Gidelim!
I knew you guys would say that!
Sizden de bu cevabı beklerdim!
Hold it, everyone!
Bekleyin!
There's no way he's alive!
Sağ olmana imkân yok!
He must be an impostor!
Sahtekârsın sen!
What are you saying, Ashura?!
Ne saçmalıyorsun, Ashura?!
Kin'emon!
Kin'emon!
Remember Lady Toki's words!
Toki-sama demişti...
Travel to the past is impossible...
Geçmişe dönemesek de...
but one can leap ahead to the future.
geleceğe gidebiliriz.
"Travel to the past is impossible"!
"Geçmişe dönmek imkânsızdır"!
Lady Toki's ability was to send people to the future!
Toki-sama insanları geleceğe gönderebiliyor.
Lord Oden died that day!
O gün Oden-sama öldü.
That fact would not change, even in the future!
Gelecekte dahi bu gerçek değişmedi.
No one can change the past!
Hiç kimse geçmişi değiştiremez!
But... it could be him!
Ama... gerçekten efendimiz olabilir!
I get that!
Anlıyorum...
But...!
ama...
Snap out of it, Kin'emon!
kendine gel artık, Kin'emon!
Look!
Bakın!
He doesn't even bleed!
Kanı akmıyor!
Impossible!
Nasıl olur?
Ashura...
Ashura...
I thought you had pledged to be my samurai.
samurayım olmak için ant içmedin mi?
Be my samurai!
Benim samuraylarım olun!
Ashura!
Ashura-san!
Now you can see his true colors...
Artık sahtekâr olduğu alenen görülüyor!
I know we all feel the same...
Hepimizin arzusu aynı yönde.
I wish he were real as well...
Karşımızdakinin gerçek olması.
But... this is an impostor!
Ama sahtekâr o!
How terrible!
Ne pis bir numara!
Who could be posing as Lord Oden?!
Oden-sama'nın taklidini yapan kim o hâlde?
It's not really him?!
Efendimiz değil mi?
Dammit!
Böyle işin...
Are you okay, Ashura?!
İyi misin, Ashura-san?!
But... his demeanor...
Ama hâl ve hareketleri...
It is exactly like Oden's!
Oden-sama'nın kopyası gibi!
The only one who could mimic him so perfectly...
Böyle iyi bir taklidi ancak...
is one of us!
bizden biri yapabilir!
So it's you!
Demek sensin...
Kanjuro!
Kanjuro!
Don't be silly! I'm Oden!
Salak olmayın! Ben Oden'im!
Ashura, forgive me!
Ashura-san, özür dilerim!
This is my fault!
Bütün suç benim!
If I hadn't failed to finish off Kanjuro...
Kanjuro'nun işini düzgünce bitirseydim...
Even the sharpest blade dulls when turned on a friend...
Keskin bir kılıç dahi dostunu kesmeye kalktığında körelir.
It must have been so hard on you...
Yüreğin el vermemiş belli ki.
Is this a painting? Where is your real body?!
Çizim miymiş bu? Çizer nerede peki?
I am puppeteering Oden from afar!
Oden'i uzaktan yönlendiriyorum.
It's quite the exhausting task!
Çok yorucu bir iş.
Hey, Kiku!
Hey, Kiku!
Your blade indeed found its mark!
Kılıcın beni kesti.
I am gravely wounded, as well!
Ağır yaralıyım.
I expect this will be my final act!
Muhtemelen bu son gösterim olacak.
But the one thing that keeps me pressing forward...
Beni şu an kamçılayan şey...
is my grudge toward the Kozuki!
Kozuki Hanesi'ne duyduğum öfke!
Therefore, before I pass away...
Yapacağım son şey de olsa...
I will pierce through the heart of the Kozuki Clan!
Kozuki Hanesi'ni kalbinden vuracağım!
As none other than Kurozumi Kanjuro!
Kurozumi Kanjuro olarak!
Lord Momonosuke is in danger!
Momonosuke-sama tehlikede!
Oh, I seem to remember hearing a voice from somewhere earlier...
Sahi, demin... bir ses duydum.
saying that Lord Momonosuke is with a kunoichi...
Momonosuke-sama bir kunoichi'yle birlikteymiş.
That must be Shinobu!
Shinobu olmalı!
Which means we can contact him!
İrtibat kurabiliriz öyleyse.
It's rather uncouth to chase down a dying man.
Ölmek üzere olan birinin de peşine düşmezsin be.
The Red Scabbards samurai will meet their demise here, having achieved nothing!
Bir şey yapamayacaksınız! Burası Kızıl Kınlar'ın mezarı olacak!
Myself included...
Benimle birlikte!
Let's go out with a bang, shall we?
Görkemli bir patlamayla veda edelim!
You guys!
Millet!
You are my friends, are you not?
Biz dostuz değil mi?
Ashura!
Ashura!
Get out of here, you guys!
Buradan uzaklaşın!
Go and stop Kanjuro!
Gidip Kanjuro'yu durdurun!
What are you doing?!
Ne yapıyorsun?
Get off of me!
Bırak beni!
Save Lord Momonosuke for me!
Benim için Momonosuke-sama'yı kurtarın!
We are in your debt, Ashura!
Çok üzgünüm, Ashura!
You bastard!
Seni camış!
How dare you get in my way?!
İşime çomak sokmasana!
Damn you! Get off of me!
Bırak lan beni!
You will never defile the memory of Kozuki Oden ever again!
Kozuki Oden'in anısını kirletme artık!
Kanjuro!
Kanjuro!
It's finally time for me, the star of the show, to take center stage!
Sonunda başrol olarak sahneye çıkma vaktim geldi!
First, I become a Kozuki...
Kozukilerden biri gibi davran...
then, I eliminate the Kozuki...
ve onların sonunu getir.
and finally, I die!
Sonra da öl!
This will be my grand finale!
En büyük oyunun perdesi kapanmak üzere.
My life is one big, beautiful play!
Bütün hayatım kalpleri dağlayan bir drama.
Jack!
Jack!
You bastard! Back for round two?!
Şerefsiz! Yine mi kaşınıyorsun?
What a pain in the ass...
Vaktimi çaldılar.
These weaklings tried to stand in my way...
Krallarını korumak için...
all to protect their precious kings!
bu beş para etmezler karşıma dikildi.
Cat! Raizo! All of you, go on ahead!
Kedi, Raizo sakin olun. Siz önden gidin.
Everyone, save Lord Momonosuke for me!
Benim için Momonosuke-sama'yı kurtarın!
Let's go, Kin.
Gidelim, Kin-san.
Yeah...
Tamam...
Be sure to catch up to us, Inuarashi! We shall await your arrival!
Muhakkak bize yetiş, Inuarashi! Seni bekleyeceğiz!
Do you intend to fight me all on your own, Ruler of the Day?
Beni tek başına mı halledeceksin, Gündüz Dükü?
We're both injured.
İkimiz de yaralıyız.
Seems like a fair fight.
Eşit durumdayız!
I didn't stay behind to settle an old grudge.
Husumetimiz için geride kalmadım.
If I let you run free, more people will get hurt! And I can't allow that, Jack!
Daha fazla unutulmaz acıya sebep olmayasın diye kaldım, Jack!
There's no view of the moon from here!
Buradan ay'ı göremezsin!
There's no poison gas, either!
Sen de zehirli gaz kullanamazsın.
Well, then... Let's find out who fate favors today.
İkimiz de elimizdekilerle yetineceğiz.
Hurry up and put it out!
Hemen söndürmezsek yangın büyüyecek!
Water! We need more water!
Daha çok su lazım! Gidip getirin!
It's you...!
Sen...
It's time to teach you fools a lesson.
Embesillere ders verme vaktidir.
I thought you were dead...
Ölmüştün sen!
How did you survive?!
Nasıl hayattasın?
How could Kaido betray me like that?!
Bana ihanet edersin ha Kaido.
There is no doubt about it, Lord Orochi...
Kaido hakikaten...
You were certainly beheaded by Kaido... once, that is.
kafanızı kesti. Bir kez de olsa.
However...
Lakin...
I'm gonna burn it all down!
Her şeyi yakacağım!
Onigashima will be a raging inferno by the time I'm through with it!
Onigashima'yı alevlere boğacağım!
There's nowhere to run in the air.
Havada kaçamayacak...
All you can do is die!
ve öleceksiniz!
I'll kill every last one of them!
Herkesi geberteceğim!
They'll rue the day they crossed me!
Burnunuzdan fitil fitil getireceğim!
Momonosuke!
Momonosuke-kun!
Can you go back to normal?
Eski hâline dönebilir misin?
You stick out like a sore thumb.
Böyle çok göze batıyorsun.
S-Sure...
O-Olur.
Stay put this time, Momonosuke!
Bu sefer çıkma ama, Momonosuke-kun!
My apologies...
Üzgünüm...
It may not look it, but I have learned to control it better...
Aslına bakarsan, artık bayağı kontrol edebiliyorum.
When I first met Luffy and the others,
Luffyler'le ilk karşılaştığımda...
I would turn into a dragon every time I got surprised or felt sad.
ne zaman şaşırsam ya da üzülsem ejderhaya dönüşüyordum.
Astonishing...
Çok şaşırtıcı.
I wonder if it's like my father's power...
Babamınkine benzer bir güç mü acaba?
If I could turn into a monster like he does, I would be of some help to everyone...
Onun gibi canavara dönüşebilseydim bir faydam dokunurdu.
Luffy is still fighting Kaido, right?
Luffy hâlâ Kaido'yla dövüşüyor di' mi?
I wonder if he's okay!
Ne durumda acaba?
I wanna take down Kaido too! As Oden!
Ben de Oden olarak Kaido'yu devirmek istiyorum!
Luffy is growing much weaker...
Çok zayıflamış dursa da...
but somehow, he is in good spirits!
niyeyse Luffy iyi durumda.
Thank goodness...
Şükürler olsun.
What?!
Ne?!
How can you tell, Lord Momonosuke?!
Siz nereden biliyorsunuz efendim?
How do we beat these guys?
Yok mu bunları yenmenin bir yolu?
They shrug off every attack we throw at them...!
Saldırılarımız hiçbir işe yaramıyormuş gibi duruyor.
That's a couple of Emperors for you... They've got some thick skin.
Namlarının hakkını veriyorlar. Derileri çok sert.
Can't they at least pretend it's making a dent?!
Biraz olsun belirti gösterin artık!
It is working!
İşe yarıyor!
After a beating like that, there's no way they're not hurting!
O kadar darbe yediler, işe yaramamasına imkân yok!
They're humans just like us!
Onlar da bizim gibi insan!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
You already tried that earlier! Think before you dive in!
Demin de yememişti bu! Düşünmeden atılma!
How can you call them human...
Aramızda dağlar varken...
when the gap between us is so big?
nasıl bunlar bizim gibi insan oluyor?
Look, if you don't think we can win, then why are you here?
Yenilmeye mi geldiniz o zaman buraya?
We're trying to figure out how to win!
Çare arıyoruz işte.
We should lure one of them away from here.
İkisini ayırmamız lazım.
Good idea.
Aynı fikirdeyim.
With the two of them side by side like this...
Bu ikisi yan yanayken...
it looks like we're in hell.
cehennem ayağına geliyor sanki.
Hell, huh?
Cehennem mi? Orayı komşu kapısı yaptım!
That light in your eyes never goes out...
Gözlerinin feri hiç sönmüyor...
Straw Hat!
Hasır Şapka!
We have the upper hand!
Avantaj bizde!